Hello friends, how are you all? I hope your
investments are
going very well. As you can see,
yesterday the financials of ICICI Home Guard were a
little disappointing, but
overall if we look at it, it has
grown quite well, so let's
quickly get to its Q3 numbers. As you can
see, there is a
lot of pressure being seen in today's market, there is a lot of pressure on the stock, so those who
want to invest in it can
also look for fresh entry. If you have already bought it in any other
school, then if it
comes at a level below your current price, you can also do
5 to 10%, so
as your average income will
improve. It is a
bleeding bank, it is an Indian
company.
If we talk about its 5 years, now its
premium price is a little less, meaning it is
available at a discount price. And if we
look at 3 years, then it is also 47, so it
is available at a very discounted rate and it is a
very
deep free company. If we look at its foot
in comparison, then the fifth number
company  Let's look at its quarterly results.
You can immediately see that
its sales were 4000. If we look at December
2100, then in
September,
I believe that
its profit, profit
before tax, all these things have decreased in the quarter-on-quarter basis. But
if we compare it,
whatever market sentiments are
seen more on quarter-on-quarter basis, then
you can see that its upside
was 6.47 in December 21, which has
increased to 7.18. But if we talk about quarter-on-quarter, then it has
fallen significantly. It had fallen by around ₹5. It is
absolutely natural that the
market sentiments will be hurt by it
and the market will
show a very negative reaction to it. And today itself I will
show you that in today's trading fashion, it is
moving very low in the trade line, a lot of pressure is being seen in
it, but friends, there is no
shortage in the company. You can see its sales growth,
that too is double digital.
Its profit growth is also double digital.
And its profits have been
excellent, even now the earnings per
share is showing 32.68, so overall it is a very
excellent company and a debt free company,
you can see that its borrowing is
255 crores, against which the
reserve after that is 8700 crores
and if we look at the promoters also,
here you can see from the share and loading pattern, the
promoters are also exactly the same, it is a little bit like this, it has
reduced but the
shareholding there is big and the shareholding of the public here is
very less, so
it is absolutely correct that today its
pressure will be seen in the market, but if
we talk about overall and long term, if we
talk about 10 years or 15 years, then the company is
excellent, so if you people have
not taken any company in the insurance sector
or you have given any SBI Life or
their policy, then I believe that it is
better that you invest in the company
and they will give better growth in the stock of the company
because
whatever the policy  It
gives only 7 to 8% return in the long run but
if you buy the stock of the same company then
you will get at least
22 to 25%
return in it, so you can see that you will
get at least 13 to 15% growth, so this is my
suggestion to you, this is the
suggestion, the rest of the investment
decision has to be taken by you, in this sector
SBI Life Insurance, HDFC Life
Insurance are
very good, but this is a little
lower in market cap in comparison to them and its potential is more, the
growth in this company is quite good, so
according to me this company
is a very good company in the life insurance sector and right now
I will also show you its chart pattern,
so you can see that as soon as the market opened,
it has fallen straight by 4.17% and if
I
look at its five-day pattern, it is a
very good five-day pattern, if we
look at it, we can see that it was
creating a consolidation at 1254
and today  It has been followed immediately
at 119, so friends, it is a very good bike right now
and if you have not bought it and you are
thinking of investing, then you
can do it in it, I will tell you its support level which comes out here,
123 has been broken, right now the
support level here is 1200 and after that
here it is 1175 and this is 1100 and here it is
1100, so you can see that if it
goes below 1100 then there will be a very good buy
and anyway, if you
want to take a fresh entry, then you can take it that right now the
price value is trading because 5
year medium PCB is down, 3 year medium is
going on, so it is a very good company, it is a
company with very good growth, if it
comes below this level, it will become very
attractive, it will become very
attractive, then you
can also invest in it, so
friends, if you liked this video, then
please like, share,
subscribe, as a display,
I will tell you guys that
I am telling you this only for educational purposes, I am
telling you information based, you have to take the decision
whether you want to buy this or not, so
if the interest rate is good in the insurance sector
then you should buy it,
hold it for at least 6 to 10 years, this company will
give you very good returns
instantly, if you buy any of its policies then it will give
you very good returns in comparison, so tell me then
thank you